Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
Let's go
This world is a flood of colors
True and false deceive our eyes
Use your heart and truly see
The truth is not so far away
Hey you good or bad, true or false
Can't escape your soul's gray smoke
Take all of your courage
And maybe save the world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Spy
The curator reveals the stolen Eternal Flame is a fake
And gives the real Eternal Flame to the police for safekeeping
Hawxing suspects Mr.K is not reliable
He decides to investigate the Illumin-Eye with Locky
The Illumin Doctrine
Mr.K, who's that guy?
Uh, well...
Huh?
It's... it's Shaker... Shaker...
Shaker? How does she know you're here?
That... I'm not sure either.
What exactly did Shaker tell you?
Well, Shaker asked me where the Illumin Doctrine was,
I said I'd lost it.
She didn't believe me, and just as she was about to attack me, you barged in.
Now the Illumin-Eye is searching everywhere for that Illumin Doctrine, which shows how important it is.
, if we could find it faster....
Mr. K, think carefully—where on earth did that Illumin Doctrine go?
Hurry up and think!
Think! Think fast!!
Ah, I remember now!
She's got it easy.
Uncle's back!
Uncle! Uncle!
Any progress on the case?
Did you catch Dorothy?
Any new updates?
That depends on Jingjing.
Jingjing...?
Jingjing, can you answer Uncle a question?
What question?
Jingjing, you once put Mr. K in your pocket, right?
Yeah.
And when Mr. K came out,
a book dropped into your pocket.
Did you notice that?
There's a ton of stuff in my pockets.
When am I ever gonna find it?
What's written on this?
I can't read any of it.
What's written in this book...
...what does it all mean?
I don't know.
Then how did you know
that the source of the Illumin-Eye's power
is this book?
The only one who can read this book
is Lord Eye.
He said this Illumin Doctrine
records in detail
the steps of the ritual to open the Gate of Civilization
and the required items.
Once the Gate of Civilization opens,
this chaotic world will be washed clean by holy water.
Everyone will cast away their filthy desires.
The whole world will be filled with love~ and ideals~
Got it?
Strange.
Why are some pages missing from this book?
This is an incomplete copy.
The ultimate ritual to open the gate of civilization
is recorded in those missing pages.
If we don't find those pages,
even if we gather all the items,
there's no way to open the gate of civilization.
Why didn't you say this before?
You didn't ask.
In that case,
Jimmy,
we must stay ahead of The Illumin-Eye
and find the incomplete ancient book.
Meanwhile,
immediately contact Tuna Town's
most authoritative archaeology expert
to help us decipher the incomplete book.
Jimmy!
Did you hear what I just said?
Maybe we don't need to search everywhere.
Why?
Because it's in the secret room in my house.
What?!
So this is your secret room
Wrong, wrong, wrong
Sorry, sorry
Sorry
Almost ready
Come in
Sorry, Locky
Officer Han and I have something important
to discuss in private
You two wait outside for a bit
Okay?
Not letting me in again
Oh~ so you have something
to discuss with Officer Han alone~
Then I won't disturb you
Kids shouldn't run their mouths
Adults...
always say one thing and mean another
Jimmy
You have a place like this?
Yeah
Just a bunch of junk
Forget that
Let's look for the ancient manuscript fragments first
Found it!
Wow, who'd have thought it was this well hidden.
The incomplete ancient book must still be safely inside, right?
Is this it?
Bet you didn't expect that.
That's right.
These match the strange script in The Illumin Doctrine.
Exactly.
I'm sure that at this moment,
you must have a lot of questions.
Yeah, I really do.
Someone's coming.
Who?
Somebody left a baby on my doorstep.
I adopted him.
And in the swaddling clothes,
there were these incomplete ancient books.
Could it be—
The baby you mentioned is—
Wait... me?
What?
Really?
That's great!
There's an archaeology PhD named Scholar Yan
who reported a case saying—
Lately, there've been
people from The Illumin-Eye harassing him
He heard we're researching
The Illumin Doctrine of The Illumin-Eye
He said he's very willing to help us
decipher the incomplete text
Seems The Illumin-Eye
is also going all out
to find this second half of the text
Luckily, both volumes of The Illumin Doctrine
we already have
Why not invite that doctor over right away
to see if he can crack this ancient book
End Credits Song
Alone, lonely and blue
That's just life
A little sadness comes through
Bidding today goodbye
Always leaves you feeling low
Look to tomorrow
Waving to me on the horizon
Each day the sun will rise and fall
Turning through time, dreaming more
Hoping for every second, every moment of life
Bright eyes are gleaming bright
Smile facing the sunlight
Steps quietly at the silent crossroads
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement, Mixing, Mastering, Mixing, Mastering
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
Look carefully with your heart
The truth is not far away
Hey you could do better
Truth and lies